<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="category_sights">Sights</string>
    <string name="category_food">Food</string>
    <string name="category_events">Events</string>
    <string name="category_spas">Spas</string>
    <string name="title_location_details">Location Details</string>

    <string name="spa_name1">Széchenyi Thermal Bath and \nSwimming Pool</string>
    <string name="spa_name2">Gellért Thermal Bath and \nSwimming Pool</string>
    <string name="spa_name3">Rudas Thermal Bath and \nSwimming Pool</string>
    <string name="spa_name4">Platinus Bath</string>
    <string name="spa_name5"><![CDATA[Aquaworld Resort Budapest \nHotel & Water Park]]></string>
    <string name="spa_opening1">Every day: 6 am to 10 pm</string>
    <string name="spa_opening2">Every day: 6 am to 8 pm</string>
    <string name="spa_opening3">Every day: 6 am to 10 pm</string>
    <string name="spa_opening4">Every day: 8 am to 8 pm</string>
    <string name="spa_opening5">Every day: 6 am to 10 pm</string>
    <string name="spa_opening_details1">Every day: 6 am to 10 pm\nPump hall: 9 am to 5 pm (except Sundays)</string>
    <string name="spa_opening_details2">Every day: 6 am to 8 pm</string>
    <string name="spa_opening_details3">Swimming pool: 6 am to 10 pm \nWellness-Sauna World: 8 am to 10 pm \nSteam Bath: 6 am to 8 pm</string>
    <string name="spa_opening_details4">Every day: 8 am to 8 pm</string>
    <string name="spa_opening_details5">Every day: 6 am to 10 pm \nPool area and Sauna World closes at 9.30 pm.</string>
    <string name="spa_contact1">+36 1-363-3210</string>
    <string name="spa_contact2">+36 1-466-6166</string>
    <string name="spa_contact3">+36 1-356-1322 \n+36 1-375-8373</string>
    <string name="spa_contact4">+36 1-340-4500</string>
    <string name="spa_contact5">+36 1-231-3760</string>
    <string name="spa_website1">http://www.szechenyibath.hu/</string>
    <string name="spa_website2">http://www.gellertbath.hu/</string>
    <string name="spa_website3">http://en.rudasfurdo.hu/</string>
    <string name="spa_website4">http://en.palatinusstrand.hu/</string>
    <string name="spa_website5">http://www.aquaworldresort.hu/en/aquaworld</string>
    <string name="spa_address1"><u>H-1146 Budapest, XIV. kerület Állatkerti körút 9-11.</u></string>
    <string name="spa_address2"><u>H-1118 Budapest, Kelenhegyi út 4.</u></string>
    <string name="spa_address3">H-1013 Budapest, Döbrentei tér 9.</string>
    <string name="spa_address4"><u>H-1007 Budapest, Margaret Island</u></string>
    <string name="spa_address5"><u>H-1044 Budapest, Íves Street 16.</u></string>
    <string name="spa_description1">Szechenyi Spa Baths in Budapest is one of the best and largest spa baths in Europe with its 15 indoor baths and 3 grand outdoor pools. Come and visit our beloved baths.\nSzechenyi Baths (built in 1913) is the most visited and much praised attraction in Budapest: relaxing, fun, affordable and, at night, romantic. In addition to the marvelous medicinal natural hot spring waters in the 18 pools, there are 10 saunas / steam cabins, several massage therapies, facial treatments, and more.  Szechenyi Spa Baths is in the biggest green park of Budapest, in the City Park, close to a bunch of Budapest attractions.\nThe  Neo-baroque palace was specifically built for hosting Szechenyi Baths as Hungary has been the country of baths (and Budapest the City of Baths) for many centuries: starting with the Roman settlers who built the first spa baths, through the 16th century Turkish occupiers who built many of the famous and revived Turkish baths in Budapest to the 19-20th century natural medical trends that promote aqua therapies and their deeply beneficial effects. \nCome and enjoy your time in Budapest in Szechenyi Spa Baths, in a beautiful, richly decorated palace. The perfect place to chill out, to get to know locals, make business deals and fall in love.</string>
    <string name="spa_description2">Gellert thermal pools, swimming pool, wave pool and spa treatments offer a great relaxation and entertainment all year round. Visit Gellert Spa Bath and experience high quality relaxation at a fraction of the costs you would pay in any western country.\nGellert Bath opened in 1918 offering medicinal water treatments using the same deep underground springs the Knights of St John used in the 12th century, and later on the Turks to feel the invigorating powers of the mineral rich waters.\nWater supply to the Bath is ensured by the spring accesses established inside the Gellért hill. The water is a hot spring water with calcium, magnesium and hydrogen-carbonate as well as sulphate-chloride, also containing sodium and with a significant content of fluoride ions.\nGellert Spa is famous for its lovely warm spring water pools, its architecture, its landscape, and also for its spa treatments, and pampering massage therapies at reasonable prices.</string>
    <string name="spa_description3">Rudas Bath is probably the most popular medieval Turkish bath in Budapest. What makes Rudas Bath stand out is definitely its 16th century core, and the fact that the bath has a special very late night opening hours every Friday and Saturday (the baths reopen from 10 pm to 4 am, both nights).\nAlso, Rudas is the only thermal bath in Budapest, which has men only and women only days on weekdays, when aprons are worn by many guests instead of traditional swimwear. Rudas Bath has recently been restored (in 2012), and is located at the foot of the scenic Gellert Hill on the Buda side.\nTurkish baths in Budapest are amazing oriental monuments with modern day facilities. Many tourists who visited Turkey will expect to see the dry Turkish sauna as a Turkish bath, but the medieval Turkish baths of Budapest are not steam baths as in modern day Turkey, but historical Turkish baths with a central octogonal shaped pool extended with other baths.</string>
    <string name="spa_description4">Palatinus on the Margaret Island is the oldest open-air beach in Budapest, always attracting a jolly crowd of people who would like to plunge into a pool in the heart of the city.\nPalatinus is found about halfway through the island on the left-hand side. Once inside, we can chill in any of the many pools, enjoy twisting slides or even practice surfing in the wave pool. After a thorough renovation, Palatinus is now open all-year-round. \nThe beautiful Margaret Bath, a complete thermal spa designed by Miklós Ybl (the architect of Budapest’s Opera House and many other significant buildings citywide), was operating in the northern part of Margaret Island until the ’50s, but had to be demolished in 1956 because of its deteriorated condition. Its function, however, was revived with this year’s completion of this new section of Palatinus, built in the basement. \nThe thermal section is comprised of a 32-34°C children’s pool with a dragon-shaped fountain in the middle, a 36°C 100-square-meter adult pool with thermal water, immersion pools with cool and hot water, a steam chamber, as well as geothermal and Finnish saunas. \nMedical services are also available on-site, the children’s pool is equipped with a children’s restroom, and the entire building complex was made accessible to physically disabled guests; we also saw a special lifting device used to help people with limited mobility descend into the water. \nBoth the indoor and outdoor pools are filled by the artificially drilled thermal springs of Margaret Island.</string>
    <string name="spa_description5">One of the biggest indoor water theme parks in Europe offers unforgettable entertainment for the whole year, for the whole family. This complex, which is located in the northern part of Budapest is waiting for adrenaline addicts with 11 giant water slides, wave and surf pools, and lovers of relaxation with saunas and thermal baths. \nExperience aquatic recreation with the help of 15 pools - our facility has a total of 19 pools with drift lanes and water jets to pamper our guests, with a total water surface of 4000 m2 all-year-long. All the way we go… in the indoor adventure pool, 11 slides of a total length of almost 1 km guarantee adventure and entertainment throughout the year. \nSauna world – separated from the busy space of the spa – is an island of tranquillity, scene of regaining health of both body and soul. Its 11 different units demonstrate the magic of sauna culture, thus contributing to regenerating both mental and physical strength, required in everyday life.  Sauna world offers Russian and Finnish sauna, as well as outdoor log sauna, steam cabin, bio sauna, infra sauna, crystal sauna, tepidarium, ice cabin, dip pool, Kneipp pool and peaceful and quiet areas to relax.</string>

    <string name="food_name1">Sir Lancelot Medieval Restaurant</string>
    <string name="food_opening1">Every day: 12 am - 1 am</string>
    <string name="food_opening_details1">Every day: 12 am - 1 am</string>
    <string name="food_contact1">+36 1-302-4456</string>
    <string name="food_website1">http://www.sirlancelot.hu/?lang=en</string>
    <string name="food_address1"><u>H-1065, Budapest, Podmaniczky u. 14.</u></string>
    <string name="food_description1">LADIES AND LORDS IF THY STOMACH MIGHT CRUMBLE \nAnd your cook be out, the solution is simple; Thy task then is only to travel, And the magic of Sir Lancelot\'s empire unravel. Ornaments on the walls, On tables candles glow, The mood of times bygone Are remembered so. And in order to keep your mouth full, we\'ll serve you a roast dove, not just a mouthful. When the bell tolls midday, the cook sets your feast on the furnace.</string>
    <string name="food_name2">Trófea Grill Restaurant</string>
    <string name="food_opening2"><![CDATA[Mon - Fri: 12 am - 12 pm \nSat & Sun: 11.30 am - 12 pm]]></string>
    <string name="food_opening_details2"><![CDATA[Mon - Fri: 12 am - 12 pm \nSat & Sun: 11.30 am - 12 pm]]></string>
    <string name="food_contact2">+36 1-878-0522</string>
    <string name="food_website2">http://kiraly.trofeagrill.eu/en</string>
    <string name="food_address2"><u>H-1061 Budapest, Király u. 30-32.</u></string>
    <string name="food_description2">Unlimited consumption(ALL YOU CAN EAT) at a fixed rate! \nIn our restaurants you can choose from a wide variety of delicious hot and cold meals and dishes for a fixed price. Our, so called, smorgasboard contains more than a 100 different types of food. You can select wine, champagne, draught beer, alcohol-free sodas, soft drinks, juices, mineral water and coffee, that can be consumed with no limit. \nEnjoy the advantages of our wide-variety-buffet system by tailoring the meals and dishes to your specific taste and needs. In our abundant offer you can find uncounted dishes among hot and cold appetizers, soups, main courses and desserts. \nBoth the fans of the traditional Hungarian cuisine and people, who are interested in the health reforms around the kitchen can locate their favourite meals at our restaurants. We also surprise those, who love the tastes of Asian cooking with our sushi offer. As part of our gourmet buffet, you can find fresh raw meat and vegetables marinated in different kinds of seasoning. On request, our chef will prepare it according to your specific desires in our spectacular grill kitchen, within just a few minutes. \nYou can have a real good time with us at your corporate or family events or at a simple Trófea lunch in the circle of your friends!</string>
    <string name="food_name3">Paneer</string>
    <string name="food_opening3">11 am - 2 am</string>
    <string name="food_opening_details3"><![CDATA[Sun - Wed: 11 am - 23 pm \nThur: 11 am - 1 am \nFri & Sat: 11 am - 2 am]]></string>
    <string name="food_contact3">+36 30-336-9060</string>
    <string name="food_website3">http://www.paneer.hu/</string>
    <string name="food_address3"><u>H-1077 Budapest, Király utca 53.</u></string>
    <string name="food_description3">A certain yellow food truck used to pop up at festivals and at Karaván in Budapest, where every meal is based on cheese; now this haven for handheld meals has a permanent parking spot in Király Street. At this two-storey unit they deep-fry, grill, and melt various kinds of cheeses – such as cheddar, Emmental, and camambert – and the outcome is always truly delicious. The breadcrumbs they use for “breading” the cheeses is homemade, and when they put the “cheese patties” in a ciabatta, and enhance it with sauces and vegetables, it is not so hard to believe that this method works very well. \nHowever, we can not only devour these cheeses in burgers, as the team of Paneer is a lot more creative than that. We can order soups, grilled sandwiches, four-cheese pasta, and even cheesecake here. Those who can’t be without meat should know that there’s bacon in the breakfast egg toast. We sometimes have to wait a little bit for our order (as everything is made fresh here), so it is not recommended to come starving, but in return, they stay open until late at night.</string>
    <string name="food_name4">Kisparázs 2.0</string>
    <string name="food_opening4">Every day: 12 am - 10 pm</string>
    <string name="food_opening_details4">Every day: 12 am - 10 pm</string>
    <string name="food_contact4">+36 30-716-9919</string>
    <string name="food_website4">http://www.parazspresszo.com/</string>
    <string name="food_address4"><u>H-1077 Budapest, Király utca 53</u></string>
    <string name="food_description4">The Parázs Presszó Thai Restaurant opened in December 2007, based in Jokai Street with the aim of bringing the amazing flavors of authentic Thai cuisine at an arm’s reach to those who prefer to linger and chat at length after a meal. \nSince September, 2013 however, it has been possible to enjoy Thai meals by Parázs in Király utca as well. Although the menu is almost identical to that of Kisparázs in Kazinczy utca, this unit comes with the novelty of Indian specialities in addition to Thai dishes. \nAt Kisparázs 2.0 you can enjoy delicious bread, meat, and other delicacies cooked in a Tandoor oven.</string>
    <string name="food_name5">Karaván</string>
    <string name="food_opening5">Sun - Wed: 11.30 am - 12 pm \nThur - Sat: 11.30 am - 2 am</string>
    <string name="food_openinn_details5">Sun - Wed: 11.30 am - 12 pm \nThur - Sat: 11.30 am - 2 am</string>
    <string name="food_contact5">+36 30-934-8013</string>
    <string name="food_website5">https://welovebudapest.com/en/venue/karavan-2</string>
    <string name="food_address5"><u>H-1075, Budapest, Kazinczy utca 18.</u></string>
    <string name="food_description5">Hungary\'s first and most succesful street food court in the heart of the party area of Budapest. \nKaraván, located next to Szimpla, is another reason to discover Budapest’s chaotic Kazinczy Street. Comprising several emblematic figures of Budapest’s street food scene, KARAVÁN gives home to numerous kiosks where we can order mouthwatering handheld meals, including the cheese-haven Paneer, Lángos Máshogy, Zing Burger, Nyakleves serving Transylvanian Székely cabbage and goulash in bread bowls, Las Vegan’s offering a vegan burger alternative, Vespa Rossa running an authentic Italian kitchen, Samurice offering vegan and meaty sushiburgers, and The Street Buffet a mecca for nachos, tortilla and pirog. For delicious chimney cake, head to Kürtős Legenda, and for miniature sausages served in a bread cone, visit Kobe Sausages. Additionally, the Karaván Drink Bar serves cold beers and tasty shots to wash down whatever delicious treat you end up choosing all year long.</string>

    <string name="event_name1">Red Bull Air Race World Championship</string>
    <string name="event_opening1">Sat 23 - Sun 24 jun 2018</string>
    <string name="event_opening_details1">Sat 23- Sun 24 June 2018</string>
    <string name="event_contact1">no phone number</string>
    <string name="event_website1">http://airrace.redbull.com/en_RU/article/2018-red-bull-air-race-calendar-launched</string>
    <string name="event_address1"><u>H-1055, Budapest, Kossuth Lajos tér 1-3.</u></string>
    <string name="event_description1">Red Bull Air Race is one of the world famous events along the river Danube, attracting hundreds of thousands of tourists to this breathtakingly daring aviation spectacle. The Hungarian stage of the international series is usually in July. \nVenue: above the river Danube, \nbetween the Chain Bridge and Margaret Bridge</string>
    <string name="event_name2">Formula 1 Grand Prix Hungary</string>
    <string name="event_opening2">Fri 27 - Sun 29 jul 2018</string>
    <string name="event_opening_details2">Fri 27 July 11.00 am to \nSun 29 July 2018 5:10 pm</string>
    <string name="event_contact2">+36 28-444-444</string>
    <string name="event_website2">https://www.formula1.com/en/championship/races/2018/Hungary.html</string>
    <string name="event_address2"><u>H-2146, Mogyoród, Hungaroring út 10.</u></string>
    <string name="event_description2">Formula 1 Hungarian Grand Prix is a unique sport event for those who love car races. Typically organized in July at the Hungaroring Grand Prix Circuit, which is a short ride from Budapest in the small town of Mogyorod. \nOne day before the whole insane Hungarian GP starts everyone (who has a ticket) can visit the pits to see the cars and the teams close up. \nVenue: Hungaroring</string>
    <string name="event_name3">Sziget Fesztivál Budapest</string>
    <string name="event_opening3">Wed 8 - Wed 15 aug 2018</string>
    <string name="event_opening_details3">Wed 8 August 6:00 am to \nWed 15 August 2018 8:00 am</string>
    <string name="event_contact3">+36 1-372-0650</string>
    <string name="event_website3">https://en.szigetfestival.com/</string>
    <string name="event_address3"><u>H-1033, Budapest, Hajógyári sziget</u></string>
    <string name="event_description3">SZIGET - ISLAND OF FREEDOM \nThe world famous Sziget Festival is on the Obuda Island, aka Hajogyari Sziget on a former Ship Factory island in Obuda district. Sziget Festival is a huge success, one of the most well known festivals in Europe – lots and lots of great music, performances, parties, funny and daring things to do (bungee jumping too), films, etc. \nHundreds of thousands of young people flood to the self contained island to enjoy the all day parties and concerts (many people put up their tents on Obuda Island to enjoy this one week unforgettable extravaganza. \nOnce you have been at Sziget Festival you want to come back for it again and again. \nPlease check the website for tickets and for more information! \nVenue: Hajogyari Island</string>
    <string name="event_name4">Fireworks Show on 20 August</string>
    <string name="event_opening4">Every year: 20 August</string>
    <string name="event_opening_details4">Every year: 20 August \n9:00 pm - 9:30 pm</string>
    <string name="event_contact4">no phone number</string>
    <string name="event_website4">http://topbudapest.org/budapest-fireworks-august-20/</string>
    <string name="event_address4"><u>H-1055, Budapest, Kossuth Lajos tér 1-3.</u></string>
    <string name="event_description4">20 aug is the ultimate firework show time in Budapest. Hungary celebrates its statehood birthday and St Stephen’s Day (the first Hungarian king) on this day with big festivities, most importantly with spectacular fireworks on its UNESCO World Heritage site, by the river Danube. \nThe fireworks are doubled in the waters of the river, which is magical in itself. A must see! The event is actually a whole day program starting on August 19, the night before the Fireworks, with concerts by the river and lots of food stalls. On Aug 20 it continues in the morning with processions and more festive events, but the fireworks and the air show are the most amazing of it all. \nThe best place to enjoy the Fireworks Show from is either the top of the Gellert Hill near the Citadel (if it is not closed down by the authorities for security reasons), or the river Danube itself from a beautiful cruise ship: Budapest Fireworks Cruise. \nVenue: above the river Danube, between the Chain Bridge and Margaret Bridge, in front of the Hungarian Parliament</string>
    <string name="event_name5">National Gallop</string>
    <string name="event_opening5">Fri 14 - Sun 16 sept 2018</string>
    <string name="event_opening_details5">Fri 14 - Sun 16 September 2018</string>
    <string name="event_contact5">no phone number</string>
    <string name="event_website5">http://en.vagta.hu/</string>
    <string name="event_address5"><u>H-1146, Budapest, Hősök tere</u></string>
    <string name="event_description5">National Gallop is a spectacular equestrian event on the historical Heroes’ Square in Budapest. The Gallop race is accompanied by a large scale food fair and cultural shows. The location is right near the City Park and Vajdahunyad Castle, so you can easily spend a day here at the festival and visit the nearby Budapest attractions. \nNot to be missed. In fact, schedule your trip for the days of the Hungarian National Gallop if you love horses, and you can afford a few days away to enjoy a Budapest visit in September (note: the National Gallop festival is not always in September – check the current date). \n Venue: Heroes’ Square</string>

    <string name="sight_name1">The House of Parliament</string>
    <string name="sight_opening1">Every day: 8 am - 6 pm</string>
    <string name="sight_opening_details1">01.04. – 31.10., every day: 8 am – 6 pm \n01.11. – 31.03., every day: 8 am – 4 pm</string>
    <string name="sight_contact1">+36 1 441-4415 \n+36 1 441-4904</string>
    <string name="sight_website1">http://latogatokozpont.parlament.hu/en/home</string>
    <string name="sight_address1"><u>H-1055 Budapest, Kossuth tér 1-3.</u></string>
    <string name="sight_description1">Approximately half a million visitors take the official tour of the House of Parliament every year. Tours start at the underground Visitor Centre in the northern part of Kossuth Square. Visually and physically impaired visitors start the group tour of the House of Parliament from this handicapped-accessible complex, where the ticket office and information booth are also located. This menu item provides useful information on your visit, including rules on visiting the gallery. \nThe building of Hungary\'s law-making body, the House of Parliament, is rightly considered among the most beautiful parliaments buildings in the world. Selected as a World Heritage site as a central element in the Danube panorama in 2011, the edifice is not only an invaluable treasure, but also the pride of the nation. It provides a home for the legislature, a place of safekeeping for the Hungarian Holy Crown, and a workplace both for the 199 Members of Parliament and for the nearly 600 people who assist them. Currently, the building also houses the offices of the Prime Minister and his support staff. \nThe shaping of the House of Parliament grew out of conscious choices of symbolism and carries important historical and political messages. Viewing it from the side of the Danube, we see the halls of the lower and upper houses rise on both sides of the dome surrounded by turrets, which evoke the memory of the bicameral parliament that was in operation when the building was being constructed. The two halls are completely identical in size and shape, thus expressing the equality between the representative lower house and the historical upper house. The dome rising between them signifies the unity of the legislature as well as serving as the venue for joint sittings of the two chambers. \nVisits to the House of Parliament are restricted during weeks in which the National Assembly holds its plenary sittings. On the first day of the plenary, the building will be accessible to visitors from 8 am to 10 am and the ticket office will be open until 11 am</string>
    <string name="sight_name2">Gellért Hill</string>
    <string name="sight_opening2">You can visit any time</string>
    <string name="sight_opening_details2">No opening time, \nyou can visit any time!</string>
    <string name="sight_contact2">no phone number</string>
    <string name="sight_website2">http://visitbudapest.travel/guide/budapest-attractions/gellert-hill/</string>
    <string name="sight_address2"><u>H-1016 Budapest, Gellért-hegy</u></string>
    <string name="sight_description2">Gellért Hill (Gellért-hegy), a gemstone of Budapest, rises above the skyline of Buda with its 235 metres. Nestled between the Elizabeth Bridge and the Liberty Bridge, it its area is shared between the 1st and the 11th Districts. This marking sight of the cityscape of Budapest has been part of the World Heritage since 1987. Its most famous cave, Saint Ivan’s Cave hides the Szent Gellért rock chapel. Gellért Hill is one of the top tourist attractions of the city thanks to the magnificent panorama from the top of its cliffs facing the Danube. You can climb the hill from two sides: take the stairs by the waterfall (only operating in the summer) at Elizabeth Bridge, or take the gradual, but somewhat longer pathway by the Gellért Bath. The latter passes a playground known for its slides, which is popular with children (and some adults as well). \nTip: Vuk Playground, a very popular themed playground with the characters of the beloved Hungarian cartoon, Vuk can be found here, just like Cerka-firka playground, a place surrounded by greenery where there’s absolutely no noise from cars. \nBesides the wonderful view, there are several attractions worth visiting: \nSt. Gellért Monument - A colonnade and the statue of St. Gellért commemorate the bishop, Gellért Hill was named after. \nCitadel (Citadella) - This fortress, built by the Habsburgs after 1849, has been a military checkpoint, prison, anti-aircraft missile launch pad, and is now a tourist attraction. \nStatue of Liberty (Szabadság Szobor) - Budapest\'s Statue of Liberty stands on top of the hill, and she can be seen from all parts of the city. The statue (by Zsigmond Kisfaludi Strobl, 1947) was erected during the Communist era. As Liberty had already become a symbol of the city, she was not removed unlike other Communist icons, such as the Red Army soldier who used to stand at her feet, allowing us to see her in her original surroundings. \nGellért Hill Cave Church (Sziklatemplom) - A network of caves exists within Gellért Hill. The first modern entrance to the caves was built in the 1920s. The Gellért Hill Cave served as a chapel and a field hospital during World War II. Today it belongs to the Hungarian Paulite order and it continues to serve as a church, but its unique setting also makes it a favorite tourist attraction.</string>
    <string name="sight_name3">Heroes’ Square</string>
    <string name="sight_opening3">You can visit any time</string>
    <string name="sight_opening_details3">No opening time, \nyou can visit any time!</string>
    <string name="sight_contact3">+36 1 322-4098</string>
    <string name="sight_website3">http://visitbudapest.travel/guide/budapest-attractions/heroes-square/</string>
    <string name="sight_address3"><u>H-1146 Budapest, Hősök tere</u></string>
    <string name="sight_description3">One of the landmarks of Budapest and the “foyer” of Városliget, the Heroes’ Square (Hősök tere) is found at the end of Andrássy út. The square was built for the millennial celebrations of 1896, to commmorate the first 1000 years of the Hungarian state. The two colonnades displaying 14 emblematic historical figures of Hungary form a semi-circle around an column, which is surrounded by the seven Magyar chieftains and topped by archangel Gabriel. \nThe Heroes’ Square is the most distinctive and most spacious square of Budapest. The Museum of Fine Arts and the Kunsthalle stand on its opposite sides. The square often gives place to large-scale public events and celebrations, while it is also an important tourist attraction. The Nemzeti Vágta (National Gallop) has also been held here since 2008.</string>
    <string name="sight_name4">City Park - Városliget</string>
    <string name="sight_opening4">You can visit any time</string>
    <string name="sight_opening_details4">No opening time, \nyou can visit any time!</string>
    <string name="sight_contact4">+36 1 374-3131 \n+36 1 374-3130</string>
    <string name="sight_website4">http://visitbudapest.travel/guide/budapest-attractions/city-park/</string>
    <string name="sight_address4"><u>H-1146 Budapest, Kós Károly stny., Városliget</u></string>
    <string name="sight_description4">Városliget (City Park) is a public park in Budapest close to the city centre. Its main entrance is Heroes\' Square (Hősök tere), one of Hungary\'s World Heritage sites. \nThe area was formerly called Ökör-dűlő, meaning \"Oxmeadow\". The first mention of the name comes from 1241 in the archaic form, Ukurföld. In the 18th century the area was called Ochsenried in German. Around 1800 the official name was changed to Batthyány-erdő (Batthyány Forest) after its tenants, the Batthyány family. The first trees and planified walkways were established in 1751 and after the public park was created in the first decades of the 19th century the present-day name, Városliget was accepted and it became the first public park in the world. \nCity Park was the main venue of the 1896 millennium celebrations of Hungary, by which time Andrássy Avenue, Millennium Underground and the Grand Boulevard were built.</string>
</resources>
